blazonry.com 2018-05-13

# Privacy Policy for blazonry.com - web.blazonry

|    

|  |  |   
**Your privacy is important to us.

At blazonry.com we have a few fundamental principles that we incorporate into our privacy policy.

**

  * We don’t ask for personal information unless we truly need it. (We can’t stand services that ask you for things like your age, gender or income level for no good reason.)
  * We don’t share your personal information with anyone except to comply with the law or protect our rights.
  * We don’t store information on our server unless required for the on-going operation of our services.

This privacy policy describes what personal information is collected and how it is used. 

## Routine Information Collection

Like most website operators, our web server software collects non-personally-identifying information of the sort that web browsers and servers typically make available, such as the browser type, language preference, referring site, and the date and time of each visitor request. This non-personally identifying information can help us troubleshoot problems and understand how visitors use this website. The information is useful for routine administration and maintenance purposes. 

Also typical of website server software, our logs collect Internet Protocol (IP) addresses which could potentially identify persons. We do not use such information to identify visitors and do not disclose such information. 

## Ads

Ads appearing on this website may be delivered to users by advertising partners who may set cookies. These cookies allow the ad server to recognize your computer each time they send you an online advertisement to compile information about you or others who use your computer. This information allows ad networks to, among other things, deliver targeted advertisements that they believe will be of most interest to you. If you would like more information about this practice and to know your choices about not having this information used by these companies, [click here](http://www.google.com/privacy_ads.html).

## Cookies

Blazonry.com uses cookies in a few programming examples for the purpose of teaching how to work with cookies. Cookies can be used to store information about a visitor’s preferences and history in order to better serve the visitor and/or present the visitor with customized content. Cookies are not inherently harmful. (A cookie is a string of information that a website stores on a visitor’s computer, and that the visitor’s browser provides to the website each time the visitor returns.)  Google, as a third party vendor, uses cookies to serve ads on this site. Google’s use of the DART cookie enables it and its partners to serve ads to blazonry.com visitors based on their visit to this site and/or other sites on the Internet.

You may opt out of the use of the DART cookie on any site by visiting the [Google ad and content network privacy policy](http://www.google.com/privacy_ads.html). 

Advertising partners in addition to Google, and other third parties may use cookies to track visitors in order to display advertisements and other useful information. Such tracking is done directly by the third parties through their own servers and is subject to their own privacy policies. 

## Controlling Your Privacy

You can easily change your browser settings to disable cookies if you have privacy concerns. Disabling cookies for all sites is not recommended as it may interfere with your use of some sites. The best option is to disable or enable cookies on a per-site basis. Consult your browser documentation for instructions on how to block cookies and other tracking uschanisms. 

## Contact Information

Concerns or questions about this privacy policy can be directed to info at blazonry dot com for further clarification. 

Note: This privacy policy is available under a [Creative Commons Sharealike](http://creativecommons.org/licenses/by-sa/2.5/) license, which usans you are welcome to use and repurpose it for your own use, just make sure to replace references to us with ones to you.
